♪ ♪
Sam, what is it?
Thought I heard something.
No, you're just
jumpy. Eh, maybe.
Here, take this.
Go ahead.
Ever hold a gun before?
No.
.357
Magnum.
Blow a hole in somebody
big enough for a
cat to walk through.
Or you can make me do
whatever you want.
Oh, you...
No. You've got to get dressed.
You're due in court.
Mr. O'Malley,
is this one of the biggest
drug cases you've ever tried?
What drug case?
There's no case here at all.
What about Rinaldi's
testimony today?
Rinaldi?
The D.A.'s entire case
is based on the testimony
of a police informant,
a known felon
who'll say anything
to stay out of prison.
Frankly, I'm amazed they're
even letting him testify,
but I guess he's
all the D.A. has.
Excuse me.
How long do you
expect this case to take?
Mr. Rinaldi, you
testified yesterday
you were present at Steven's Bar
on the night of August 22, 1989.
And at that time, you
overheard my client
buy $11 million worth of
cocaine from a Mr. Pedro Cruz.
Is that correct?
Yes, it is.
And isn't it also true
that four months ago,
you were arrested for
possession of cocaine?
Yes.
Yes, and at that time,
you offered to testify
against my client, Mr. Sam
Chandler, in exchange
for immunity from prosecution.
That doesn't change the facts.
Oh, the facts.
The facts.
We'll get to the
facts in a minute.
Were you or were you
not granted immunity?
Yes, I was.
Yes, you were. Now, the facts.
The night of August
22, 1989, you say
you went to Steven's
Bar with Mr. Chandler.
And when you overheard
this conversation,
where exactly were you sitting?
At the bar.
You, Mr. Chandler and Mr. Cruz
were sitting at the bar?
No, they were at a table.
Oh, they were at a table,
and you were at the bar.
So, in other words, you
weren't sitting with them
when you overheard
this conversation?
That's right.
Now, Steven's is sort of a
small singles bar, isn't it?
Yeah.
Yeah. And it was a Friday night,
so the place must
have been jammed.
Yeah.
What would you say,
there were about 60,
70 people there? Yeah.
About the same number
as in this courtroom? Yeah.
Yeah, something like that.
Your Honor, with
the court's indulgence,
I would like to try and
reconstruct the circumstances
at Steven's Bar on
the night in question.
Objection, Your
Honor. Relevance.
Overruled.
Given the potential damage
of this witness's testimony,
I'm going to allow
Mr. O'Malley to continue.
Thank you, Your Honor.
All right, ladies and gentlemen,
uh, we need your help.
We need you to pretend
that you're at a
bar, it's Friday night,
you're out with some friends,
uh, having a couple of drinks,
talking, laughing, having
a good time, okay?
It's okay, folks,
you can do this.
You heard the judge.
He said it was okay, right?
Uh-huh. Yeah, no.
I said a good time.
A good time, yeah.
Folks, come on.
I've heard rowdier
groups at a funeral.
Louder. Louder, everybody.
Would you say this is
about the distance it was
to, uh, Mr. Chandler?
I-I don't... I can't
hear you. I...
You having a
problem, Mr. Rinaldi?
I can't hear you.
Folks!
Quiet, please.
Mr. Rinaldi can't hear me.
And if you can't hear me now
in this courtroom, Mr. Rinaldi,
how in the hell
can you sit there and testify
under penalty of perjury
that you could
overhear a conversation
at a crowded singles
bar on a Friday night
between my client and Mr. Cruz
when you were sitting at a
bar halfway across the room?
You know what I
think, Mr. Rinaldi?
You didn't hear one word
of that conversation, did you?
Not one word.
No further questions.
Has the jury reached a verdict?
We find the defendant,
Samuel Chandler, not guilty.
Thank you, ladies and
gentlemen of the jury.
This court stands adjourned.
It's okay, Deputy.
That's my wife.
Congratulations, Mr. Chandler.
She's something.
Ah, you were
wonderful, my darling.
It's good to have you back.
Yes. All right.
Hey, Sam. Hey, congratulations.
I hear O'Malley was terrific.
Quite a show, quite a show.
Pour me a drink.
Sure.
I take it you all heard
from Jack Rinaldi.
I'm not paying
him another penny.
Relax, Bobby.
Did you get a tape?
An excerpt. I think we
got to do something.
You know,
I expect Bobby to
go off half-cocked,
but you, Al, too?
I thought you were
smarter than that.
Just a minute.
Yes?
David.
What are you doing here?
That's my line.
Dave, let's be calm about this.
It's not serious.
Where's Sam?
I don't know.
Where is he?
At Todd's Grill.
Sam, that tape
gets in the wrong hands, it
could mean life for all of us.
That's not what Rinaldi
wants; he wants money.
A few bucks.
The moment he turns that tape
over to the police,
he's out of business.
A million dollars is
more than a few bucks.
You kill Rinaldi,
the police are
gonna come after me.
Take a vacation.
The Greek Isles are
beautiful this time of year.
Perhaps I didn't
make myself clear.
If I hear that Jack Rinaldi
slipped in the shower,
or hung himself because he
was distraught or depressed,
I'll know who killed him.
You threatening me?
I just came this close
to going to prison.
That's close enough!
David!
What are you doing here?
Stay away from my wife,
or I'll kill you! Cool it!
I'll kill you, you
understand! Hold it! Hold it!
I'll kill you. Come on, come on.
Hello. Maintenance.
♪ ♪
Eh, boy.
End of the ride.
This is your favorite spot, huh?
What are you doing here?
David, that was a
dumb thing to do.
Punching out Sam Chandler
is like taking on Mike Tyson.
It's really stupid.
Did anybody see you?
Well, we were in the
back room at Todd's Grill.
Jim Steinbach,
Al Brackman and
Bobby Boyd were there.
Do you know who
those fellas are?
Ben, at one time or another,
I've represented all of them.
Not for jaywalking, I'm sure.
Not one of them ever
got convicted of a crime
while I was representing
them, including Sam Chandler.
Sam Chandler.
Crook. Big dope dealer.
Not according to the jury.
One of his friends killed him.
With your gun. What
was your gun doing there?
Well, they stole
it out of my office.
Look, I already told the police,
I can account for my actions
at the time of the murder.
I was being hit up
for free legal advice
by a bellman at the
hotel. There's no bellman
there that fits
your description.
Oh, really? Well,
that's a surprise.
Come on. I'm being
framed, Ben. Obviously.
Look, as soon as I get out here,
I'll write you a check for the full
amount of your fee. I-I assume
our-our fees are comparable.
Well, what do you
get for a case like this?
$125,000 plus expenses.
Huh.
Is there... is there a
problem with the figure?
Oh, no, no.
No, I-I usually get,
um, a little bit more.
Good morning,
Mr. O'Malley. They're all here.
I thought you rented
small temporary quarters.
I did.
Come on.
Morning. Morning. Good morning.
I've had my staff
stay on here in Atlanta.
We've put our heads together
and given the case some thought.
Now, we already have files
on everyone who heard me
threaten Sam Chandler. David?
I think we should put a
tail on each of them, though.
David? Now, the medical
examiner found that
Sam's right index
finger was broken
just before he died. David!
What?
Um...
Did you sign me on,
uh, to defend you?
You want me to send them home?
Well, we're both not
going to represent you...
People?
Uh, that'll be it for today.
We'll arrange
your transportation
back to New York first
thing in the morning.
Thank you. Thank
you all for your work.
Can I at least, uh,
give you the files
on Bobby Boyd, Jim
Steinbach and Al Brackman?
Fine.
Here you go.
Is, um...
Is your wife still in town?
Yeah. She's at
the Wilton Towers.
She won't talk to me.
I don't think she'll
talk to you, either.
Maybe not.
What do you want me to do?
Oh, go back to your hotel,
look at television, read...
Ben, I'm a good investigator
and a damn good
attorney. You know that.
Well, then, maybe you
should represent yourself.
No.
Anything else?
Well, yeah.
Uh, most good lawyers
make lousy defendants.
I'm sure I would,
too. We all have
reputations.
You're a jet setter.
Hot tempered.
Uh, two-fisted drinker.
I want you to watch your temper,
stay in town, and
lay off the booze.
We need for the
jury to like you.
It's very important.
Of course, you know that.
Yeah.
You know, Sam's got a
security system on the house.
It's off.
Go. Get to work.
Now, if someone found that
tape before us, we're dead.
Hey, why don't you
try the bedroom?
♪ ♪
I got it.
Let's get out of here.
Place looks like a cyclone hit.
Tell me about it.
Detective Cox.
Mm-hmm?
Conrad McMasters.
Oh. You work with Ben Matlock.
Yeah. What do
you make of all this?
Routine burglary.
You don't think this
has anything to do
with Sam Chandler's death?
Sure. Whoever did it knew the
house was going to be empty.
Thieves would have
to be out of their mind
to break into Sam
Chandler's house.
A lot of thieves
out of their minds.
And don't these
things usually indicate
if the alarm has gone off?
It wasn't on.
Man gets murdered one day,
house broken into the next.
One thing has to have
something to do with the other.
Yeah, they might.
Excuse me.
Hey, Bobby.
Whatcha say?
Get out of here.
Bobby, I'm sorry
about your brother.
I'm sorry I couldn't defend him.
You don't like people
like Greg and me.
That's why you
didn't represent him.
Now, what do you want?
You knew Sam Chandler.
Yeah. He was like
a brother to me.
Well, how did you feel
when he, uh, started, um...
you know, with your sister?
You got a lot of nerve.
You come in here, a place
you've been told not to come.
Then, if I understand
you correctly,
you suggest I might have killed
a man who was like family to me?
What's the matter with you, huh?
Don't you have any
damn respect? Renee?
Thursday morning, I was
at your place, wasn't I?
Yeah. Eddie?
Sam? Show Mr. Matlock the door.
Never mind. Never mind.
Never mind.
Mr. Brackman.
Hey, Mr. Matlock.
Hi, how are you? How are you?
Hello, boys.
This is, uh, Matthew,
and this is Josh.
Oh. Hey. How are you?
Listen, would you
mind taking a couple
pictures of me and the kids?
No. Get-Get together there.
C'mon. Get close there.
Where do you look through?
Oh, you look through...
There you go. Uh... Yeah, okay.
One, two, three.
There. Then...
You advance it to the right.
Let's do another.
This-This? Yeah.
Okay. Gotcha.
And one, two, three.
That's...
One more for safety, okay?
Give me a great big grin.
There you go.
Oh, that's great.
Thank you. Yeah.
Listen, why don't
you guys go look
at the big engine
down there, all right?
Yeah. Come on.
Yeah.
Nice boys.
Thank you.
They changed my life.
Yeah. Is that the case?
I'm a husband, parent...
respectable man.
Well, uh...
excuse me for
saying it, but, um...
uh, would a respectable
man, uh, have meetings
with Bobby Boyd
and Jim Steinbach?
We're friends.
We've been friends for years.
I have done everything
I can to escape my past.
I'm a legitimate businessman.
Once in a while, I get
together with old friends,
and we have a couple
of laughs. Is that a crime?
No, no.
David O'Malley said that
when he got to the restaurant,
all of you were yelling at Sam.
Sam liked to argue.
You can think whatever
you want of me.
Those kids are
what's important to me.
And if you think that
I'd go into business
with Bobby and
Jim, you're crazy.
What about Sam?
Sam's dead.
Atlantic City.
A couple years ago.
You went into a big
hotel deal with Sam.
Very lucrative.
He cut you out.
That was business.
It was nothing.
Then you won't mind my asking...
Where I was when Sam was killed?
On the money. Right.
My wife and I are trying
to have another child.
Well...
We were trying.
Oh.
♪ ♪
You following me, or
you watching the bar?
Both.
Angela Page. I work for
David O'Malley.
I know.
Conrad McMasters.
Get in.
You're David
O'Malley's investigator.
You look surprised.
I am. I don't expect to
see a woman like you
doing this kind of work.
Ah, I was a legal secretary.
I didn't like it.
But you like following dope
pushers and murderers.
Finding out their
dirty little secrets
and staking out
joints like this.
Yes, I do.
And hopefully, it's useful.
Do you like jelly beans?
Yes.
Mmm!
I thought Mr. O'Malley sent
everybody back to New York.
Yes, he did.
You don't take orders very well.
I don't take orders at all.
Got to go.
It's been...
brief.
All right.
Hey.
What did he want?
Who?
The guy you were talking to.
Why don't you ask him yourself?
Next time I see you,
I won't be this nice.
Oh, Ms. O'Malley.
Yes?
Uh, I'd like to talk
with you about Sam.
No.
Surely, you could
spare a moment.
No! I said no.
I've spent 15 years
married to a criminal
lawyer.
I know who you are,
and I know what you want.
You want to use my life as
David's defense, don't you?
You want to put
me on trial. I'm sorry.
My life is my business,
and I'm going to
keep it that way.
Well, she did talk to me.
Hmm...
Come on in.
Be with you in a minute.
Okay.
You use all this stuff?
Religiously, every day.
Looks painful.
You get used to it.
And it pays off a lot better
than some of the
stocks I've been in.
Oh.
I'm at 186.
Yeah?
You look thinner than that.
That's my cholesterol.
Oh.
Okay.
Please, sit down.
Oh.
Let's get right to it.
Sam Chandler.
Quite a guy.
David O'Malley does
one phenomenal job
getting him off,
and then Sam sleeps
with his wife in return.
Yeah. Yeah.
I remember your father's death.
So do I.
At the time, there
was some speculation
that Sam had a hand in it.
It wasn't speculation.
I never got involved
in my father's business.
I never wanted to.
Then, one day, I got a call.
My father was shot
four times in the head
while he was getting a haircut.
I knew what he did.
I wasn't surprised.
I was 23 at the time.
Now, I could have retaliated,
which means taking
over my father's business
and starting a war, or
I could choose peace.
I hated Sam for what he did,
but I chose peace because
I didn't want to get involved.
I didn't want that kind of life.
Mr. Matlock, I didn't
kill Sam Chandler.
If I'd have wanted to do that,
I'd have done it
a long time ago.
Well, I-I-I still
have to ask you
where you were that morning.
Jogging.
I jog every morning.
Well, uh,
did... did anybody, uh...
People see me?
I don't know if
anybody remembers
seeing me that particular day.
Bobby Boyd's here.
What are you going to do?
I'm leaving. Jack, he's
crazy, and I'm not
staying here without you.
Vicki, huh? Don't worry.
You're safe. He's
looking for me.
Well, what should I tell him?
Tell him you haven't
heard from me,
you don't know where I am.
Hey, hey, hey.
Huh?
Hey, they'll pay me
off in a couple of days.
Soon as I get the
money, we're gone.
Okay. Go.
Yeah, Vicki.
How are you, huh?
I'm fine. Good, good.
Come here. Come here.
You look exhausted.
Had a bad night.
Mmm.
Staking out the house?
Yeah.
Mmm!
Popcorn?
Mm-hmm.
Done a lot of this?
Yeah.
Vicki, we don't
have to do it this way.
I don't know where he is.
You can do better that.
I swear I don't.
Please, stop it.
You tell Jack he's
got 24 hours to call.
If he don't...
I'll be back.
Hi, ma'am.
My name is Conrad McMasters.
May I talk to you for a moment?
What is it? I
need to talk to you
about the guy who just...
Hi. Oh... oh, are you all right?
Let's get some ice on that.
He was looking
for her boyfriend, Jack Rinaldi.
Oh.
David!
Hi. The cleaning crew let me in.
What are you doing
looking through my stuff?
Well, the preliminary
hearing is tomorrow, Ben.
I want to see what you have.
You got anything at all?
You know Jack Rinaldi?
Yeah, I know him.
He seems to be the
key to this case. No.
He's totally unimportant.
And if that's all you have,
we're going into court
tomorrow with nothing. David, I
don't want you looking
through my stuff.
I've got other
cases with secrets
that have nothing
to do with you,
and I don't want
you looking at them!
I just wanted to
see what you've got.
I... you work so
differently than I do, Ben.
We're not going to
trial in the morning.
We've got time.
I know I work
differently from you.
And I know that must make
you nervous. I guess I'd
be nervous, too, if
I faced the prospect
of going to prison
for the rest of my life.
I can step aside.
I can step aside, you
can get somebody else,
or you can handle it yourself.
But, like they say, a man
who represents himself
has a fool for a lawyer.
Here.
Take the rest of
Conrad's popcorn,
go home and think it over.
But whatever you decide,
you're not getting my fee back.
Thank you.
I want you to find Jack Rinaldi.
And make him disappear.
Keep me posted.
♪ Won't you come
home, Bill Bailey? ♪
♪ Won't you come home? ♪
♪ She moaned the
whole night long ♪
♪ I'll do the cookin', honey ♪
♪ I'll pay the rent ♪
♪ I know I done you wrong ♪
♪ Remember that rainy evening ♪
♪ I threw you out ♪
♪ With nothing but
a fine-tooth comb? ♪
♪ I know I'm to blame ♪
♪ Ain't that a shame? ♪
♪ Bill Bailey, won't you
please come home? ♪
♪ Yeah! Yeah! ♪
Yeah.
♪ Bill Bailey, won't you
please come home? ♪
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
♪ Bill Bailey, won't you
please come home? ♪
Oh. Yeah.
That was good. All ready
for Biloxi, Mississippi.
Close.
You're my lawyer?
Well, hell, I get
to have a little fun.
Uh-huh.
You want something?
Chili's pretty good.
Maybe later.
So, what's so urgent?
Right here.
♪ Bailey, won't you come home? ♪
♪ Bailey, won't you
come on home? ♪
Well, anyway...
I got a call from the D.A.
right after you left the office.
He's, uh... he's
got another witness.
Who?
Your wife.
My wife?
Yeah, she's going
to speak to motive.
Susan is going to testify?!
Cool it, cool it, cool it.
Uh, Sally?
Uh, bring us... uh... bring us a
couple cups of coffee, sweetheart.
The assistant D.A.
said that she'll testify
that you're so jealous of her,
that when you found her
over at Sam Chandler's place,
you went into a murderous rage.
This is a riot.
It isn't true?
Yeah. It's-It's half true.
I am jealous...
because I love her.
So much, in fact, that
I always forgive her.
Which is pretty
stupid, I suppose.
Then you did go
after Sam Chandler?
Yeah, but Sam wasn't
important. I-I... I just wanted
to make sure that Susan
was going to come back.
Then she's lying?
Yeah.
Can you corroborate?
Uh... the maid... Shirley.
Yeah, we could...
we could fly her down.
Detective Cox? Hmm?
Can you identify
this revolver for us?
This is my tag.
That's my mark.
I found this weapon at
the scene of the crime.
It was later determined
to be the gun
that was used to
kill Sam Chandler.
And to whom is
this gun registered?
The defendant, David O'Malley.
Thank you, Detective.
Nothing further.
Mr. Matlock.
No questions, Your Honor.
You may step down.
Call your next witness.
The people call Susan
O'Malley to the stand.
Mrs. O'Malley, how long have you
and David O'Malley been married?
15 years.
And during that time,
did you ever have an
affair with another man?
Yes.
Did your husband know?
I think he suspected
I was having an affair
with Sam Chandler.
Mrs. O'Malley, would you call
your husband a jealous man?
Oh, yes, very. Was he
possessive? Completely.
And did your husband
ever learn about
your affair with Sam Chandler?
Yes. The night
before... Sam was killed,
David found me at Sam's house.
How did he react?
He became violent.
What do you mean "violent"?
He grabbed my face
and squeezed it very hard.
He's a very strong man.
I didn't know what
he was going to do.
And then what happened?
He threatened me.
He made me tell
him where Sam was.
And where was that?
Todd's Grill.
And then what did
your husband do?
He finally let go of me,
and he ran to his
car and took off.
And could you describe
his emotional state
as he left you that evening?
Oh, yes, he was in
one of his jealous rages,
but he was... more angry
than I've ever seen him.
He scared me.
Thank you, Mrs. O'Malley.
No further questions.
Mr. Matlock?
Uh, Mrs. O'Malley,
did the D.A. tell you
that you did not have to
come here and testify today?
Yes.
So you, of your own free will,
volunteered to
come here and testify
against David O'Malley?
Yes.
You mad at him?
D-Do you want to see
your husband go to prison?
I believe that David
killed Sam Chandler.
Oh!
So you're here for justice,
and not vengeance?
Oh, yes, that's right.
Uh, Mrs. O'Malley,
isn't it true that you
have had, uh, affairs?
Yes.
And aren't-aren't they often
the act of, um...
an angry person?
Yes, I suppose they can be.
But you-you-you've
chosen to testify
against the man who bought
the very dress that you're wearing.
Who provided clothing,
housing for you.
Your every need for the entire
15 years that you were married.
Is this the way you
show your gratitude?
Mr. Matlock, I'm not
a vindictive woman.
You couldn't prove it by me.
Now you-you've testified...
you've testified
that David O'Malley
is a jealous, possessive man.
How-How did he
demonstrate that to you?
Well, he would get furious
if I were just going to go
have lunch with a man.
He would order me
not to go. Hmm.
Well, did you do what he said?
No.
Oh. And did he rave and yell
a-and become very unpleasant?
Yes, he would... he
would scream at me
if I just danced with a
younger man at a club.
Does the name Edward Campbell
mean anything to you?
Well, yes. Edward is a close,
old friend of David's and mine.
He's a closer friend to
you than David, isn't he?
In fact, isn't it true
that you had an affair
with Mr. Campbell
seven years ago?
No. Even though
Mr. Campbell lives in New
York, he does have a telephone.
Surely you must know
that someone from my office
has spoken with him,
don't you?
You're under penalty of perjury.
We had an affair.
And this husband...
this jealous, possessive
man, found out about it,
didn't he?
Yes.
But he didn't rave
and yell or even
go after Mr. Campbell, did he?
No. He forgave you, didn't he?
Yes, yes, that time he
did, but he was always
fighting with me and screaming
at me because of other men.
Come on, Mrs.
O'Malley, if that were true,
your housekeeper
Shirley Lipton would have
heard at least
some of the fights.
Oh, yes, she did.
Shirley heard them.
Shirley Lipton
is prepared to testify
that David O'Malley is not
a jealous, possessive man.
Quite the contrary...
he loved you so much,
he forgave your affairs
and indulged your whims.
There were no
fights. There were no
"jealous rages,"
as you call them.
Isn't that a true picture
of David O'Malley?
Oh, you can just trot Shirley
out here on her crutches
and get all the
sympathy you want,
but the fact is, she's lying.
Move to strike the
witness's last statement.
So ordered.
Uh...
Y-Your Honor, may I
have a half-hour recess?
Is everything all
right, Mr. Matlock?
I'm not sure.
Take an hour and
we'll call it lunch.
This court is
adjourned until 1:15.
Stay here, stay here.
Come in, Ms. Lipton.
Come in. Have a seat right here.
That's good. I-I have a...
Good. I have a few
things I need to run through
before we go into the courtroom.
Of course. Now...
how long has it been since
you've seen Mrs. O'Malley?
It was six months
ago when she fired me.
Have you talked
to her since then?
Not once.
Ms. Lipton, are you aware
that perjury is considered
a serious crime in this state
and is punished severely?
Why are you telling me this?
I want you to also know
that at this very
moment, my investigator
is going over your bank records.
Oh.
Is that a problem?
How did Susan
O'Malley know that
you're using crutches?
You only broke your
leg two days ago.
And you say you haven't
spoken with her in months?
Well, maybe David told her.
David told me
he hadn't spoken with her
since the night before the murder.
Somebody's lying.
David O'Malley is
paying you, isn't he?
Yes.
And he is a jealous,
possessive man,
and they did have loud,
ugly fights, didn't they?
Yes.
Ms. Lipton,
give him his money back.
What the hell are you doing?
You had her. Why'd
you let her go?
You set me up.
What?
It was a dumb move, David.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You staged all this.
Somehow you got
Susan on that stand.
You paid Shirley to lie.
You filled me with the lies
so I could take Susan apart.
You're crazy.
A lying, cheating wife...
the worst possible witness.
She'd make the D.A.
look desperate.
Discredit his case, make it
look weak and without merit.
And you arranged all that.
You're actually standing
there accusing me of this?
Shirley admitted it.
I know your wife cheated on you,
and I know you're
madder than hell,
and I don't blame you, but...
how in the world did you
get Susan on that stand?
You're not back together again!
I'll tell you how I got
her back on the stand.
By explaining to her that it was
in her best interest
if she wanted a
speedy, lucrative
divorce settlement.
I'll tell you the truth...
I'd love to drop this damn case.
You've lied to me.
You've perverted a system of
justice you're sworn to uphold.
Ben, you want to drop the case,
there's obviously
nothing I can do about it,
but do me a favor...
don't stand here
and try and tell me
that you've won all your
cases by playing it straight.
Because I know
better. I know you.
You're like me. You like to win.
And you will bend the rules.
No.
Not all this.
What are you going to do?
Don't know.
Gonna quit?
Ben Matlock's office.
Hmm!
Ben Matlock.
Uh-huh. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Be there in a half hour.
Jack Rinaldi.
Hey, don't
go in there.
He'll spook Jack Rinaldi. Hey!
www.tvsubtitles.net